Hello friends and there true health to
with you
uh my name is
and um
as you know
um Tuesday
I'm also a member of living and I am
feel to share with you
health messages that I am hoping of
benefit to every other Tuesday
and uh we're talking about health
particularly about nutri one of my my
specialty to talk about sh but
this time
pray.
I'm learning getting better.
So before pray okay
for the opportunity you give us
um this technology
and about how to take
ask you to be with us
so that the technology
that is said that everything that we may
be for honor and glory in Jesus name we
all right to this presentation I hope
you have other uh find out you know by
the way
oh
uh producer
is
she was having some tech difficulty know
she's working very very hard. Uh I'm
going to try to maybe do the
the audio
with
Okay. She said we'll be our producers
working very hard on it.
[Music]
the same difficulties that I'm having
with your
sounding very very um I don't know what
I don't know what
um I've tried rebooting my rebooting my
tried rebooting my browser. Try
rebooting my
Is there another browser? Um Um
I don't know.
Oh, did it clear up now? Oh, did it
clear up now?
You sound great.
Yeah, I swear to
before.
Oh, yeah. But you're still coming in
somewhere. It's still
Oh, I see.
I don't know what's causing it. Um,
do you
I can try rebooting my computer one more
time. I can try my
but other than that I don't know what I
don't know what to do.
Okay. Can you hear me? Can you hear me?
Yes, I can hear you. It's still bad.
bad. Ohly.
Wow.
Yeah. So, it's definitely whatever.
It's We're gonna have to end the stream
and try again.
Um,
I need to create a whole.
Okay.
Okay. Okay.
Oh my goodness.
Um,
do you want to email you the link? I'll
email you the link.
Do I have to disconnect? Yes, you will.
I press leave. Um, yeah, hold on a
second. Let me make sure you
um Well, they're they're
pause for technical difficulties, but
reply
Okay. Um.
Oh, come on.
Why is that one so smoothly? Really
don't.
Okay, I sent you the link to the new
one. I will put that in the chat as
well.
So right right now where I'm even then
click on the other um
I think
have to rejoin
Do you think I
This is
okay. I set the new link out to
go on.
Okay.
Okay. I'm going to leave this one down.